YG's new girl group BLACKPINK
set a new record
by reaching number one
in terrestrial television music programs
in just 14 days after their debut.
There are 27 videos,
including the music video
for DDU-DU DDU-DU,
that reached
hundreds of millions of views…
Setting various records…
Surpassing the global pop stars…
DAY 319
BLACKPINK is finally
having their first concert in Jamsil
in their second year since their debut…
-Hello, we are BLACKPINK.
BLACKPINK started their world tour
with their first concert.
January 31, 2021, celebrating
the 5th anniversary of their debut.
BLACKPINK is welcoming fans
around the world with online concerts…
Fans around the world
are looking forward to seeing
BLACKPINK in person
to celebrate their 5th anniversary.
I think those were really hectic moments.
Because it was our first time.
I'm facing towards the stage right now
and those were the seats for BLINKS.
There was a stage
that stretched out to the front
and we ran underneath the stage.
I think the most nervous moment is
when we walk towards backstage
with the thought of meeting our fans
and performing for them
I think that’s the most nervous moment.
I feel alive when I see the fans
singing along to my song and enjoying it.
That feeling of success like,
"Wow I did it."
They’re dancing together like me
when I feel that
I think that’s when I feel most alive.
Wouldn’t there be much to talk about
when we meet? From now on?
So, I'm looking forward to it.
Performing with the band during
the concert is definitely really great.
The energy is actually unreal.
How do we go in here?
So that BLINKs can also enjoy
the wait for our next performance.
Please look forward to it!
We worked really hard
to prepare for this concert
so I hope you watch it
more than ten times.
See you soon, bye.
Let's go! let's go! let's go!
What are we doing right now?
Emcee Girl.
We got here today for the rehearsal.
For what tomorrow is this rehearsal for?
I believe it's a rehearsal for The Show.
I wanted to make it more perfect
because I was not satisfied,
I wish I had more time…
I’m so nervous…
It was the most fun…
and the best time of my life.
I’ll continue to remember
that moment, that feeling
A lot of things happened,
there were happy times
and there were sad times.
I think those were the happiest times.
When I try to think about
the difficult times
I strangely can’t remember them.
I just erase everything
that has to do with difficult times
without even knowing from my mind
I don’t think I’m over positive
and outgoing person.
I am normal person just like everyone else
every day I’m like this.
I knew what I wanted to do
since I was young
I believe I am very lucky person.
I had a clear goal
to be a singer in the future.
I worked hard to make my dream come true.
I try to think that I am happy without
having to stress myself too much.
I hope for the others to think like that.
I think I thought that I am
a lot stronger than I thought.
There will be times when I feel hurt
or go through hardship but
during those times my way of overcoming
is preparing more for this
or focusing on thinking about
how I can better move forward.
Attitude towards life?
That’s a hard one.
Well…
I think I just live
by enjoying every moment.
What I felt throughout the process is
that if I think too far ahead about
things that haven’t happened yet
I could get anxious and worry about it
and there are many things I overlook.
So I try to live in the moment
and try to have fun, I think.
It's almost time to meet all the BLINKs
from all over the world
who have waited so long.
I am very, very nervous
but as much as you’ve waited
I am going to show you the best.
Show us a lot of support and enjoy it.
Thailand is also Lisa's hometown
I think it's more meaningful to start
our world tour in Lisa's hometown.
Starting from Thailand,
we're going to North America
and Europe
to meet BLINKs around the world.
I'm so honored and looking forward to it.
BLACKPINK's world tour itself
is still very unfamiliar to me.
I still can't believe it.
I prepared a lot of fun stuff
for our concert
and want to do more exciting things
in different countries.
That's how I feel.
I hope many BLINKs around the world come.
It's gonna be fun.
It was very touching.
I think I'm very lucky to see them,
I could really tell how hard they tried.
From beginning to end
I want them to take care of themselves.
I hope everyone is healthy because
they have to go to concerts
around the world.
We're going
to visit BLINKs in other countries
Please wait a little more.
We'll be there very soon
and we'll show you a great performance.
Wait a little bit BLINKs.
I just love how four young women
be themselves.
Hello, I’m Lisa.
I’m a little shy
but I want to tell everyone…
Thank you so much.
I think our identity is rather fixed
I like to think that
we have a lot of pride
in having color black and pink
but because of that
we’re still in the process
of continuously experimenting
and fortunately rather than
not being able to predict it,
we are going forward in the direction that
we want
and just enjoying the whole process
because of that.
We all grew up in different cultures
and various cultures overlapped
and a group was born.
But instead of forcing them into one
we worked as a group
without losing each of our individuality
and I think that rather emerged
as the color of the group BLACKPINK.
I think we shine the brightest
when we do what we love to do.
Now that’d be music, right?
When we are fully expressing
what we want to express.
That’s when we shine the brightest.
So I think it’d be great for us to show
a lot of things
that we enjoy doing in the future.
As we do this,
because we’ve always done it thinking,
"We could show something like this,
this time we can show this."
I think we can show different sides
of us now onwards too.
We plan on continuing to do what we want
and show it.
Five years is not too short and not too
long of a time, right?
But a lot of different things happened.
There were happy times, and sad times.
I think those
were the happiest times in my 20s.
When we were on tour
I’d always feel hectic thinking about
which city we have to go next and such.
But then seeing this video
it seems like we laughed a lot
and really enjoyed our time together.
When we debuted,
and had different experiences
there was a fear about whether
or not we were doing well
and felt uncertain about some things.
When we had our first concert
what we say on stage is
also a very important part of our concert.
I was really nervous, like,
"Let’s not make any mistake."
It’s already been two years
since we debuted a little more than that.
And to be able to have a concert
at such a big venue in Korea
in Seoul like this…
Even as I’m saying it I feel like
I’ve improved very very much.
And that was possible thanks to BLINKs.
Right, everyone?
We’ve been together since day one.
I like to think that
we’ve grown a little bit
seeing how we’ve become
more comfortable with making a speech
and taking care of each other.
I like to believe that
we still have that energy
from when we were trainees.
I’m so moved,
thank you all so much for coming.
Because it’s the four of us
let’s trust the four of us
and have more fun since we started saying
that often.
It became more enjoyable
to take on new challenges
and we got more excited
and looked forward to things?
I think we grew further.
We are always here for you, BLINKs,
so please stay with us BLINKs.
When the four of us are together
we always laugh and talk
just like we did when we were trainees.
It’s just so fun to work together also.
I think we’re the same.
Now we don’t even have to say a word
we just look at
each other’s eyes and know.
Tell us, Lisa.
Yes. Thanks to all of your support.
And your love I will strive to work harder
as Lisa of BLACKPINK, everyone.
I love you, BLINKs.
BLINKs.
We just finished the last US show, yay.
Wow, I still can’t hear.
Is my voice coming out alright?
I’m so sad it’s already over.
It feels bittersweet.
Over the past month and a half
there were
many new and exciting experiences.
Still, I had a lot of time
to relax in different cities.
And it was great.
We performed a lot
and it was a meaningful time.
I think I enjoyed every moment
more than I thought.
It was a meaningful tour,
like a surprise gift.
What I felt the most
during the tour was that…
it was really a time for me
to rethink myself as BLACKPINK.
I honestly don’t think we’ve changed much
just because it’s been five years.
We haven’t changed much,
but it’s more reassuring
to have fans by our side
that always support us for five years.
There will be sixth
and seventh anniversary in the future
but because it feels like
we’re getting stronger over the years
I really like the feeling of us and BLINKs
becoming a lot closer.
I feel like I cried a lot
over the five years.
When I watch the videos
from my fans I tear up.
I was so touched
when I just saw that video.
Even now as I’m talking
I feel like I’m going to cry.
Because I think those were
such happy times.
Five years ago we were five years younger
and it was probably the same
with our BLINKs.
As we keep growing
I was very very happy
to be able to be with BLINKs
and I miss them so much since we haven’t
been able to meet lately
but just as much, next time we all meet
I’m so excited at the thought
that we’ll be able
to really happily greet them.
Thank you so much
for always worrying about us
and we miss you so much.
Because BLINKs are always there
by our side loving us
no matter what we did
or happened that year.
It makes us want to further move forward
I hope you go
all the way together with BLACKPINK
as lifelong companions.
Thank you and love you always.
When we talk about how we feel inside
I always have nothing to say
I feel very shy about it but…
What should I say?
To keep it short
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much
for loving BLACKPINK Lisa.
When I was a kid I never imagined…
I could be loved
by people all over the world.
I don't know how to express
my feelings other than thank you.
As we go up the stage like this
we can see
the light sticks shaking and the cheering.
It’s so pretty.
Some people make it go beep beep beep
because you can set it like that.
Every time I hear it I just get so excited
and feel so encouraged.
-BLACKPINK!
We’ll cherish this truly precious memory.
Thanks to all of you supporting
and loving us wholeheartedly.
We’ll keep this memory
and strive to grow further as BLACKPINK.
Thank you.
Just once more,
we’ll see you once more closely
before we go.
So pretty, our BLINKs.
Please support us
and stay excited till the end.
-We love you.
THANK YOU FOR BEING
THE LIGHT OF MY YOUTH
So in short, can I do it with a gesture?
Okay, I’ll go with my gesture.
-Since everyone expresses differently…
-Right.
Thank you for reacting.
Wow, but what is this it’s great.
Can you just finish like this?
Shall we try it together? Shall we?
Like this.
So funny.